Default credentials matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Open cloud storage matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Unnecessary services matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Debug configurations matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Secure baselines Hardening standards Configuration management Selected ISO mappings for
this topic include 8.
9 - Configuration management; 8.
8 - Management of technical vulnerabilities.